Hello hello everyone we are making a series
about comparison of term insurance
this series can help you a lot
in selecting insurance if you have
not seen our last video which was
about comparison of ICC Loot Chief Loop
then you must find it in the link description the
comparison we are going to do is about Max
Live smartphone vs Chief product first of all
we will talk about some company's details
Max Life
Insurance Twelve Ven was earlier
known as Max New York Life Insurance
but now it is in joint venture
with Subscription To Insurance Company which is
an insurance company having
subscribe settlement ratio of 9%
plus in the last 15 years it has shown
very good results in settlement ratios their
headquarter is in Delhi
ICICI Prudential was started in 2012 it has been
in the top companies list since inception
it is in joint venture with company which is
headquartered in Mumbai and
Nottingham around 1600 crores tisouriyan rahe hain Planets ki
Baat  Let
us first discuss those points which
both the
companies provide flexibility in
premium payment. You can take single payment in this, you can
select limited payment option
and regular payment option. On the
other hand, there are twos in both the companies.
Riders are optional. You can take accidental
insurance plus critical illness rider.
In Max Life, you can
take accidental insurance of
maximum Rs 1 crore and can
take up to Rs 2 crore in the same year. Very soon the
company gives flexibility to the policy holder
that he can increase his time
as the responsibility increases like after
marriage. Next point,
returns paper gives a vague option that
if they want returns and premium at any crossroads, then
they can take it, through which your and
riders are transferred to you on that off. The
first option in the benefit options
is that if there is a death, then both the
companies have the option to make the payment. The
second option  Income option means
that the percentage of time received by the policy holder every year gets
divided into monthly income.
In Max Life, it also goes up to 15 years. The
third option is increasing these
two.
110% of what you are getting per month gets added to
your income tax rate to
beat inflation on interest.
This option is
also available in both the companies. Now let's
talk about some differences which are
different in both the companies. If you
talk about the basic class nine life cover of this company, then in
such a case, if the
policy holder becomes permanently disabled due to an accident, then all these options get
appointed.
If the policy holder gets a terminal illness, that is,
any critical disease,
after which the policy holder cannot subscribe, then
in this case the company makes the
payment in advance. So, both these features are
not of ICC. Next option is available for
you. Life cover plus. This means that
if the policy holder dies tomorrow, then the
lump sum amount will be given to his nominee.  It is
plus 0.4 percent which is received every month as an option, for example,
if you have a policy of one crore, then
its nominee gets ₹1,
plus every month you get
40 thousand rupees as a monthly income
and the second option is your life cover plus
increasing income, that is, you get a
lump sum on the date, plus the
monthly income of 0.4 percent is also
increased every year at percent interest so
that you can cut the bonus,
for example, if you have a policy of 1 crore, the
policy holder gets ₹4000
and after the percent increase, the
subscription starts for the next year, according to this
point the
subscription of the policy holder keeps increasing,
for example, if it is 15 lakh, the
last point is this, every year the
insurance coverage keeps decreasing,
which, for example, if you have a
policy of one crore, then it will not be done in the next year,
this is a very good attractive option in
which  Out of these, 35 are available in this building itself, the
remaining four are available in Max Life, the
rest are approximately like maximum 1665 years, there is a
festival of small things
between both the companies, as we
told you that we take your views
in the last that according to us which company
is good and you people should take this,
we
are your union, according to us if you go, then
according to us
you people should consider ICC Potential because
it is a very strong company and
insurance is a long-term commitment, which is
very important for their financial background,
this is our opinion, Max Life has
also got very good results in the last few
years, so you should
select your plan as per your choice, you should
decide on your own, do your study yourself,
Sunidhi, all the information
about the comparison of both the plans, we keep bringing such user information,
Supreme, like our channel,
subscribe, thank you
for watching